export type Data = {
    id: number;
    question: string;
    answer: string;
};

const data: Data[] = [
    { id: 10, question: "What is the capital of indis??What is the capital of indis??What is the capital of indis??What is the capital of indis??What is the capital of indis??What is the capital of indis??What is the capital of indis??", answer: "delhi" },
    { id: 11, question: "What is the capital of japan??", answer: "tokyo" },
    { id: 12, question: "What is the capital of japan??", answer: "" },
    { id: 13, question: "What is the capital of indis??", answer: "delhi" },
    { id: 14, question: "What is the capital of japan??", answer: "tokyo" },
    { id: 15, question: "What is the capital of japan??", answer: "" },
    { id: 16, question: "What is the capital of indis??", answer: "delhi" },
    { id: 17, question: "What is the capital of japan??", answer: "tokyo" },
    { id: 18, question: "What is the capital of japan??", answer: "" },
    { id: 19, question: "What is the capital of indis??", answer: "delhi" },
    { id: 20, question: "What is the capital of japan??", answer: "tokyo" },
    { id: 21, question: "What is the capital of japan??", answer: "" },
];

export default data;
